Hey Troy, did you plan this to happen at
halftime of the Chaos game?
>> Yeah, he just texted me. Um, we wasn't
able to talk, but I know he's proud of
me.
>> Hey, I know you've had a pretty eventful
pre-draft process. Just, you know, what
does it feel like now to have it all
wrapped up and to be a New Orleans
Saint?
>> Yeah, it feels great. Shoot, I never
stopped working, so I was cool with it.
I never stopped working out. Never got
out of shape. Never had to restart my
soreness process. Never had to get my
feet callus back up. So, shoot, I'm
ready to hit the ground running right
now. Jordan, did did you uh get to meet
Chris Lave on on your visit?
>> For sure. Yeah, he sat in our meeting
with Coach Dub. Um we talked on the
phone a couple of times. So, for sure.
Yeah, that's my dog. We we locked in and
we ready to work.
>> What do you like about his game?
>> Uh he's different. He can do it all.
He's he's a speedster, so he can take
you over the top, but at the same time,
he can settle it down just as fast. So,
he he can do anything and everything at
the position. He play slide. He can play
outside. He's kind of like me, but um
but he's proven himself. I say that.
What do you think about playing
alongside a lot of it?
>> Ah, it's going to be amazing. Shoot. Um,
take pressure off each other, make make
our jobs easier, and shoot. I feel like
um us one-on-one shoot,
>> it's going to get ugly.
>> What can you bring What do you bring to
the table?
>> Say that again.
>> What can you bring to the Saints?
>> Um, just uh versatility. I feel like
just just another playmaker in the room.
I feel like a guy that you come to on
third down is that's always going to be
open in a sense. So just just just
playmaking ability and then um just a
just a guy that's always in the
building, always guys trying to meet new
teammates, see see where their story
came from and just pouring the guys love
on guys and I feel like yeah that's what
I bring
about Shuck right now. Like what do you
know about his game? How would you
describe his game?
>> He's a great quarterback. He played half
the season and he finished finalist in
the offensive rookie of the year. So
great player. He's going to continue to
do big things. He's very smart. He knows
how to read the defense. Always on time.
He's a he's a great quarterback. Came
with to get to work with him.
>> Jordan, what triggered your emotions?
>> Um, it's just just where I came from.
Like, I wasn't supposed to be here. I
was 5'4 my sophomore year. I had no work
ethic until my junior year. It was I'm
not supposed to be here without without
God blessing me with an amazing family,
an amazing sport system, and just God
bringing me the right people in my in my
circle. I wouldn't be here. So, it's
it's all credit to God and just what he
did with with my life and all the people
around me. What? How does it feel that
you'll get to play so close to home
being a Texas native?
>> It's amazing. Um, sure. I can go back
home whenever I need. My brother has a
house in Dallas, so I got a spot to stay
there, but um, it's amazing. I'm ready
to get to work. I'm ready to get back to
the South. Been on the West Coast too
long.
>> What changes with your work ethic your
junior year?
>> Um, my brother just shoot me to the to
the weight room one time and shoot, I
decided that's what I want to do instead
of playing the video game. It was all my
brother. I just
I just I just tagged along with him and
he brought me to Lifetime. We had
Lifetime Fitnesses um passes and that's
all we used to do every day.
>> And Jordan, a lot's been uh talked about
when it comes to your injury history and
things like that. What would you like to
clear up about that or or say about, you
know, your process?
>> I'm going to give myself the best
opportunity to stay on the field and be
as healthy as possible. I'm going to do
everything in the weight room. I'm do
everything in nutrition. I'm have my own
chef. I'm going to get my massage on the
same day every week. I'mma have my
regimen so down to a tea that there's
I'm gonna give myself the best
opportunity. We do play football, but
I'm gonna give myself the best shot
possible.
>> Is that something you've talked about
with other players before? Like is that
why you have that so locked down
already? Like talk to other players
about
>> war. Hans war.
>> Did you have more interaction with the
Saints than maybe some other teams? And
how would you describe the way the
interaction with the Saints has gone
over the last couple of months?
>> Yeah, they they was trying to get under
my skin. That's that's how I kind of
knew they was really thinking about it.
um actually seeing if they was going to
take a chance with me. So, they was
trying to get under my skin. They was
trying to see see um what I say in
response.
>> Like what? What do you mean?
>> Um they we was at the combine. He was
like he had told me something but it
wasn't the truth. Trying to see if I was
going to agree with it and I kind of
just didn't agree with it because it
wasn't the truth.
>> Who's the he? Who are you talking about?
>> For 10 years.
Jordan, Jordan, when did you say to
yourself during your college career that
you would be in this position to be a
first round?
>> To be honest, I feel like
>> this I keep I just keep getting better.
That's all I can say. Like I keep
getting better. I just want to continue
on that track. Uh work works. I'm just
going to continue to work and shoot.
Yeah, that's all I can say. I'm going to
just continue to get better, continue to
learn, continue to soak in, take as many
pictures as I possibly can, and just be
the best player and get my put my best
foot forward.
>> Hey, Joey, how big was this night just
for you and your family with with this
going on and the uh in game three going
on?
>> Yeah, it's crazy. My brother had hit a
three right after the Saints had called
me. It was It was like a dream come
true. Um Um Yeah, it's it's amazing just
having a brother that's playing in the
NBA and playing in the NFL. He just was
the blueprint for me. So, it's it's
everything to us. Um, I know my parents
are super super duper happy and feel
like they can have a little side of
relief now, I'm guessing. And yeah, we
we just ready to go. We we we a
close-knit family. Um, it's just us.
Like, we don't have too many outsiders.
Just it's just us. We're going to pour
everything into the Saints. Um, and
yeah, we're all going to put our best
foot forward.
>> What do you know about the city of New
Orleans? Have you been here before? to
be hon I had never been in Louisiana
until um I came on the top 30 visit to
be honest even even being a neighbor
state in Texas but um I know I know the
food is real good I know we ride on the
water I know as the south so you going
to have the same uh similar people as we
did in Dallas but um yeah y'all pass
some great players over there Michael
Thomas y'all had Alvin Kamar for a long
stretch y'all just got Travis ETN who's
a great player been following him so I'm
I'm ready to get hit the ground running
a great offense and I think we can do
some special teams especially in our
division
>> what's favorite food from Louisiana?
>> Um, we had went to um the little oyster
spot. It was it was fire. Oh, I can't
>> um the little popular one. I can't
remember. We had probably
>> Drago Drago. We probably had probably
had 100 100 oysters.
>> Jordan, did you say you were 5'4 as a
junior in high school?
>> I was 5'4 as a sophomore in high school
and then I developed the work ethic
again my junior year.
So, like when did this actually become
like a reality for you that like the
idea of of an NFL playing career?
>> Yeah, obviously like we was we was going
to try the football thing. Like I've
never known myself without a football.
So, we knew we was going to try it. See
if I can go to college for free. But to
be honest, it didn't hit till
probably the end the end of the season
this season to be honest. I feel like I
just like I said, I just continue to get
better and I feel like I just want to
stay on that track. I just want to
continue to take my off seasonason so
serious and yeah, be the be the best
player I can be.
You could tell, you said you could tell
when it was that the Saints interest was
real in you. How real was your interest
in this team?
>> Oh, very real. Um, I knew I knew they
had a quarterback. That was that was a
big thing. And then also a receiver on
the other side, a great receiver on the
other side I can learn from and just see
how he handles his business. So, it's
it's like a match made in heaven. And
we're and we're the Saints. So, that's
that's
>> Jordan. What was it like being coached
by Hines Lord?
>> It it was amazing. And um he he was
everything to me. He played 14 years in
this league. So he's made every snake.
He made every right decision. And he
just throughout that he gained knowledge
and wisdom and he just poured all that
into me.
>> Hey Jordan, what was kind of your
mindset when you um after your freshman
year when you you know you left
Colorado?
>> Um I just I just knew like
>> I played my freshman year obviously so I
had some film. I knew I was going to get
more offers than I had out of high
school. So I just knew I had to keep
working. Like that's all my brother
would preach to me. It's hard work,
discipline, continue to be who you say
you want to be. Like just keep going,
man. You and anything's possible through
Christ.
>> Jordan, you said all the things you plan
to do to to work on your health. Was
there anything that you identified
during the process? I know sometimes
guys who have had a hamstring issue,
there was just a story about like Jason
on his shoe size. I mean, any that that
that's controllable for you.
>> Yeah, my hips were tight. My hips were
super tight, but I was so strong in the
hips that I would just overcompensate
for the tightness. So, I've been getting
my hips real loose. I don't think it was
really a hamstring problem. It was
probably a hip problem or my glutes
wasn't activating. So, we're working on
like the the whole because it's all
connected. So, we're working on
everything. We're not just working on
the hamstrings. So, I feel like we got a
good sense. I got a good team behind me
and yeah, we're we're ready to go. I
feel like we've been preparing for a
couple months now and yeah, I think I'm
the readest I'm going to be. And how did
you feel like you handled handled, you
know, going through that knowing that it
might delay your NFL dream or I mean
like how did you handle that adversity
of the injury?
>> Um, you talking about the knee injury?
>> Well, I guess like when you had another
one last year that that maybe missed
some games and and some testing time.
Did you how did you hand like you know
>> I don't I don't try to look too much
into the future. I try to take each day
for what it is and try to too many
challenges in one day to to be worried
about the next one. So, just like I
said, bro, continue to put your best
foot forward and work your tail off.
>> When did you hit your growth spurt?
>> Junior year. I grew to six foot.
>> Hey, uh, talk to your old your old
quarterback about falling into Louisiana
here.
>> Yeah, he text me. I gotta text him back
when we get on this phone. Ben doing all
this media stuff. That that's that is
real dope. I ain't I didn't realize
that.
Are you ready to tackle the humidity
here in Louisiana?
>> I'm from the south, man. That ain't that
ain't nothing.
>> It's a different heat.
>> Yeah, it is. It is. It's dry in Arizona.
It's real real dry. You under the shade,
you fine. You can't run from that heat
in in the south. But I'm ready. Oh, is
Louisiana hotter than Texas or about the
same?
>> The humidity a little different.
>> Yeah, because you on the water.
Are we saying that you grew eight inches
from your sophomore year to your junior
year?
>> Yes, sir.
>> My brother was always super tall and my
feet was always super big, so we knew I
had a chance.
>> What stood out to you about your um your
top 30 visit with the Saints?
>> Um it it was everything. Everybody was
cool. Everybody was real about their
business. is like Coach Dub, he he's not
going to play around me. He's going to
he's going to give me all. He's going to
um get on my butt when I need it and
he's going to be my biggest fan at the
same time. So, just how serious they are
about winning football games and I feel
like they're on the right right track
and we're we're ready to turn this thing
around. But, I don't think I don't think
it's too bad. So, I don't think it's too
much turning around, but we're going to
be just fine.
>> As this draft was starting tonight, did
you think like was this one of the spots
that you thought this could be my spot
at eight to the Saints? Was this one of
the ones that like you had an aster by
this might be me? For sure. Um, for
sure. Yeah. Yeah, for sure.
>> I knew it was I knew it was like five to
11, but yeah, I knew I knew this was for
sure just just based off the top 30
interviews, just based on how they was
uh treating me and how they was talking
to me. So, definitely knew it was a spot
that could happen.
>> When you didn't go at five, like when
you didn't go at five, you said to get
nervous or wonder when your name was
called or were you able to was like
having the Cavs game helpful? Like what
kind of going through your mind there?
>> Um, I I was I was chilling. I know I
know God has a plan, so no need to
worry. Anxiety ain't going to do nothing
but make the situation worse.
>> What do you like about Kell Moore's
offense?
>> Um I we briefly went over it when he was
going over the plays at the combine and
uh Dove, he was coaching it. He was like
um Pacific Northwest State and I said
Ohio.
He got he got on my tail. He was like no
that's not Pacific Northwest. He was
like Washington. Washington. So I know
um y'all have like different groupings.
I know you have a lot of different um
concepts to the right and to the left.
So, I know the quarterback can audible
some stuff if he sees stuff he like, but
yeah, I I really like it and I feel like
it's it's going to be nice.
>> What are your impressions of coach do?
>> Let's take a couple more, guys.
>> Um yeah, real real cool dude. Real real
about football. Loves football. He wants
to see the best out of his players. He's
going to treat everybody like his like
his sons. And I and I was just getting
that feel just off the top 30 visit. So,
I believe he's telling the truth and
he's he's going to give me his all for
sure. And I'm ready to go. What you what
goes into making you such a good route
runner? Like how how how did you develop
like the detailedness and kind of your
suddenness and everything?
>> I was short. I was short. I was short
playing slot. Um I could only play slot
because I was so short. And then when I
grew, I I just took that slot route
running ability to the outside and yeah,
just kind of kept developing, get
bigger, faster, stronger. Got my power
output up and shoot the limit. I feel
like
>> I think, correct me if I'm wrong, your
workout was last week in front of
scouts, right?
>> Yeah. How important was it for you to to
just go out there and show what you do?
>> Um, yeah, it was it was very important.
I know there was still some some
question marks over my head, but um just
wanted to answer as many as I possibly
could.
>> Anything else?
>> Congratulations.
Thank you. Thank you. See y'all soon.